[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is version control?",
    "correctAnswer": "The practice of tracking and managing changes to software code",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Only updating OS/languages to non-beta versions",
      "Ensuring dependencies of the same library share the same version",
      "Remembering to update your SDK"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is a branch in git?",
    "correctAnswer": "An independent line of development",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A node of a binary tree",
      "The entirety of the project",
      "A piece of code being reviewed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is a merge conflict?",
    "correctAnswer": "Local changes compete with code on the same line(s)",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "When your PR is blocked by another developer",
      "Cached data not matching new code changes",
      "Writing code in an unexpected language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is CI (continuous integration)?",
    "correctAnswer": "The practice of automating the integration of code changes into a single project",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The practice of automatically deploying code changes to a testing/production environment",
      "The practice of every change that passes the production pipeline is released to customers",
      "The practice of manually integrating the code changes into a single project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is CD (continuous delivery)?",
    "correctAnswer": "The practice of automatically deploying code changes to a testing/production environment",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The practice of automating the integration of code changes into a single project",
      "The practice of every change that passes the production pipeline is released to customers",
      "The practice of manually deploying code changes to a testing/production environment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is git merge?",
    "correctAnswer": "Taking the independent lines of development and integrate them into a single branch",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The process of moving/combining a sequence of commits to a new base commit",
      "Matching your cached data with your data source",
      "The practice of merging your every active branch simultaneously"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is git rebase?",
    "correctAnswer": "The process of moving/combining a sequence of commits to a new base commit",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Taking the independent lines of development and integrate them into a single branch",
      "Refreshing cached data to a previous state",
      "Returning to the latest version of the repository"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How do merge and rebase differ?",
    "correctAnswer": "Merging preserves the history of the branches, rebasing rewrites it",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rebasing preserves the history of the branches, merging rewrites it",
      "Merge can be done locally while, rebase can only be done in GitHub",
      "Both are the same, the difference is based on programming language used"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is git stash?",
    "correctAnswer": "Temporarily store your changes you have made to your working copy, usually to be applied later",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Store you working changes to a text file for you to reference later",
      "Stores your working changes to your commit without needing a message",
      "Used to store changes to specific storage, like a file or USB drive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is git status?",
    "correctAnswer": "Displays the state of the working directory and the staging area",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Displays and compared the commits and branches from your local branch and another branch",
      "Displays if the branch is safe to push",
      "Displays current errors and potential lint issues"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What is a PR (pull request)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lets other know about the changes you have pushed from your branch into the development branch",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The request to pull code from the repository to your device. Needs credentials",
      "The process of moving/combining a sequence of commits to a new base commit",
      "The practice of managing and disseminating information from an individual or an organization"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is CD (continuous deployment)?",
    "correctAnswer": "The practice of every change that passes the production pipeline is released to customers",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The practice of automating the integration of code changes into a single project",
      "The practice of automatically deploying code changes to a testing/production environment",
      "The practice of cherry picking your branch to merge it into production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What does the command git config do?",
    "correctAnswer": "Used to set Git configuration values on a global or local project level",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Used to view the Git configuration values on a global or local project level",
      "Used to configure which files will be ignored upon pushing the branch",
      "Used to configure which language Git should expect in this repository"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What does HEAD represent in git?",
    "correctAnswer": "The current commit you are viewing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The master branch",
      "The branch you branched off of",
      "The one who created the repository"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is the command pattern you follow to push your code?",
    "correctAnswer": "[git add .]-> [git commit -m \"commit message\"] -> [git push]",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "[git push], Android Studio is aware of my local changes and pushes only those",
      "[git add .]-> [git commit] -> [git push]",
      "[git push --set-upstream origin <branch_name>]"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is git pull?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fetches the content from the remote repository and updates local repository to match it",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The command needed to start a pull request",
      "Downloads commits, files, and refs from the remote repository into your local repository",
      "Pulls the code from previous commit under your profile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is git fetch?",
    "correctAnswer": "Downloads commits, files, and refs from the remote repository into your local repository",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fetches the content from the remote repository and updates local repository to match it",
      "The command needed to start a push request",
      "Fetches the credentials of your GitHub account"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is git diff?",
    "correctAnswer": "Used to compare two commits, branches, or files across revisions or branches",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Displays the state of the working directory and the staging area",
      "Pulls the code from previous commit under your profile",
      "Displays your cached data with your data source"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which is not a benefit of version control?",
    "correctAnswer": "Easy duplication of code",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Traceability",
      "Compliance adherence",
      "Documentation history"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is meant by the repository in git?",
    "correctAnswer": "The entirety of the project",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The development branch",
      "The code you are working on",
      "The GitHub website"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is the least important thing you should look for in a PR?",
    "correctAnswer": "Does the code run",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Is the code following best practices",
      "Does it solve the problem in the ticket",
      "Is the solution code being covered by tests"
    ]
  }
]